masterkreatif.com 2013-11-23

# Privacy & Policy | masterkreatif.com » Free Fast Download Direct Links

The following is the Privacy Statement for web masterkreatif.com 

Please read the following statement carefully. If you have any questions please ask us via the [](http://www.masterkreatif.com/p/contact-us.html). 

**Email address**

You can choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our site. We agree that there will never share your email with third parties and will remove your email at your request. We do not currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email address to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form. 

**Ownership Information**

masterkreatif.com is the sole owner of all information collected at our site except when we mengkutif from a website or blog, then we will include the source site. 

**Comments or Message Boards**

Web masterkreatif.com provide commentary box. We do not always actively monitoring all incoming comments and information about them is for entertainment purposes only. If, for one moment there are issues that are considered inappropriate, then by any means, we will to remove them. 

**Cookie**

Currently we assign cookies for readers to save their preferences. This data is not shared with third parties. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you prefer. 

**Third Party Cookies**

Many of our advertisers use cookies to determine how many times you've seen the ads. This is done to limit the amount of the same ad will be displayed. who did not have access to this data. 

**Traffic Report**

Masterkreatif.com industry standard record IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time the page is loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular. 

**Legal Proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy, but if necessary by a legally valid reason masterkreatif.com may need to disclose information. 

**Business Transitions**  
**  
**

If masterkreatif.com acquired by or merged with another company, our web assets, including personal information, will likely be moved to a new company. 

**Links**

Web masterkreatif.com often lead direction to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of this site. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by masterkreatif.com. 

**Notification of Changes**

Masterkreatif.com Privacy Statement at any time subject to change without prior notice. 

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy masterkreatif.com, Information, Share, please [](http://www.masterkreatif.com/p/contact-us.html)
